DAWID FLORIAN



CONTACT

532 645 060

dawidflorian99@gmail.com



dawidflorian.pl



In linkedin.com/in/florian-dawid



github.com/git-df

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE,

ENGINEER "Politechnika Rzeszowska" 2019 — 2023

COMPUTER SCIENCE,

TECHNICIAN "Zespół Szkół Elektrycznych i Ogólnokształcących w Krośnie" 2015 - 2019

SKILLS

.Net Core | C#

Razor Pages | MVC | Blazor

REST API

HTML | CSS | JS

MS SQL | PostgreSQL

LINO

Entity Framework Core

MediatR (CQRS)

Mapper

Identity

XUnit

GIT

Postman

C++

IIRA

Confluence

Slack | Zoom | Teams

SUMMARY

I graduated this year with a degree in Computer Science and have been immersed in the world of IT for over 8 years since my high school days. Along the way, I've absorbed a wealth of knowledge and skills in the field. My fascination with the .Net platform began during my freshman year at university. Throughout my studies, I've executed multiple projects using these tools, including a car rental system (built with Blazor, Rest API, MS SQL). This journey has taught me extensively, particularly in the hands-on application of these technologies.

EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR IT SPECIALIST

9bits | 07/2022 — NOW

MS SQL, PostgreSQL, Postman, Swagger, Datadog, Grafana, Nagios, OpenSearch, PagerDuty, Kibana, RDP, SSH, JIRA, Confluence

For over a year, I have been working in the position of a junior IT specialist at a company specializing in software development. I am involved in:

- Monitoring of services and servers.
- API testing.
- Manual and regression testing of web and mobile applications.
- Analysis and resolution of problems reported by customers.
- Documentation management.

ACADEMIC INTERNSHIP

Soft Integration | 2012 — 2014

WordPress, HTML, CSS

During the summer vacation, I completed an internship by working at a company specializing in the development and expansion of ERP software. My tasks included:

- Updating content and adding new elements to the company's website.
- Testing solutions being implemented into the software.

CERTIFICATES

2021 - Architecting with Google Compute Engine - Google Cloud 2019 - E12, E13, E14 - Technician IT

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the European Parliament's and Council of the European Union Regulation on the Protection of Natural Persons as of 27 April 2016, with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC.